(Sheldon:)The spiral of scales open in
(Sheldon:)the Fibonacci sequence.
(Sheldon:)A fact that,
when you tell your brother,
(Sheldon:)gets a golf ball
thrown at your head.
(Amy:)So, why do you feel
you need to save these things?
(Sheldon:)I'd like to say it's nostalgia,
(Sheldon:)but every time I think
of throwing anything away,
(Sheldon:)my ears start to ring,
(Sheldon:)and I get butterflies
in my stomach.
(Sheldon:)And then it feels like
(Sheldon:)the butterflies
get eaten by rats,
and then, the-the rats
get eaten by...
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Amy:)I get it. I get it.
(Sheldon:)It ends with dinosaurs.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry
if you think less of me.
(Howard:)I don't.
(Penny:)Really?
'Cause every time
I come in here,
(Sheldon:)I think less of me.
(Penny:)Why?
(Sheldon:)Because I'm a fraud.
(Sheldon:)No. I purport
(Sheldon:)to be a man of the mind.
I've been such a-a vocal
champion of The Singularity,